SAM PETERSON

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

peter2020@fakemail.com

30 Rockefeller Plaza, NewYork, NY

EDUCATION

University of Kwazulu-Natal Bachelor of Computer Science and Information Technlogies June 2017 - July 2020

University of Kwazulu-Natal Bachelor of Computer Science Honours July 2020 - Present

SKILL

Wordpress, Joomla HTML5, CSS, JS Adobe Photoshop Sketch

ABOUT ME

Results driven individual with four years experience desiring to bring engineering and telecommunication experience to a software engineering position at ABC Company. Searching for the oppotunirt to bring 8+ years experience, and server maintenance to a software engineer position with ABC Company incorporating critical thinking, problem solving and leadership

EXPERIENCE

BACK-END DEVELOPER

Google Inc

January 2017 - August 2017

- Facilitate back-end aspect of things
- Make sure everything was insynch with everything
- · Communicate well with the front end stuff
- Make sure data storage and app is in synch

TESTER

Microsoft

June 2019 - Present

- Maintain server
- Provide and facilitate end user assistance
- Maintain computer paraphernalia
- Make sure data storage and app is in sync

REFERENCE

Kutlo Sek, Google Inc

Senior Developer

Email: kutlosek@fakeemail.com

Steve Jobs, Apple Inc

CFO

Email: stevejob@apple.usa

John Kazisky, Washington Party

Politician

Email: johnpol@gmail.com